scoophub.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Most Popular - ScoopHub

The information of the customers is considered to be as very important for ScoopHub.in. Therefore, this privacy policy is the manifestation of the categories of personal information, which are collected and stored by ScoopHub.in. All these are described in this document in detail. Moreover, it is also stated here about the way we handle the information you confide with us. The information is in no way misused or abused, so you can be absolutely confident in storing your information in this website.

 **Log Files**

As seen with a lot many other online sites, we at ScoopHub.in too have a system of log files. This is nothing but the process of helping a visitor of the site to get logged into our website. This is considered as a standard procedure, which is followed by innumerable hosting companies. This also abides by the analytic process of hosting services. In most cases, the information you share on this website during the logging process is generally inclusive of IP (internet protocol) addresses, along with ISP and browser type. This also includes referring and exit pages, date and time stamp as well as the probable number of clicks a visitor is making while he is on a ride of this website.

The information that ScoopHub.in requests you to submit, is actually significant in the process of analysing trends, administering the website. This information is also used to maintain a track on the visitor’s stay at the site as well as the movements one makes and the subsections of the sites one explores. Demographic information about the visitor is then gathered. Nevertheless, IP addresses, as well as other information related to the visitor, are generally not associated with any such information, which is likely to be personally identifiable.

 **Cookies along with Web Beacons**

The other aspect of ScoopHub.in is that it has the practice of using cookies. They are generally made use of in order to save information regarding the preferences of the visitor, to enhance the surfing experience of the visitor of the web page, along with information related to the pages that are accessed by the visitor usually. All this helps you to experience a customised way of surfing our websites. We at ScoopHub.in make sure that you have the smoothest way of accessing our website as per the type of the browser you use.

 **Double Click DART Cookie**

Google uses cookies in order to serve ads on ScoopHub.in.

Google also uses the DART cookie to display ads to our visitors when they come to our website

Users are able to block ads anytime by logging on to the URL:

http://www.google.com/privacy_ads

 **Advertising Partners**

Some of the mentioned advertising partners associated with us may use cookies and web beacons:

  * Google
  * Amazon
  * Commission Junction
  * Linkshare
  * Ebay
  * Yahoo! Publisher Network

 _Each of these partners also has a separate privacy policy for themselves._

All the aforementioned ad servers send their links and advertisements to  your browser directly. This implies that they may use your IP address and ScoopHub.in has no control over or access to this.

 **Children’s Information**

Parents are requested to keep an eye on the online activities, which children include them in. ScoopHub.in does not allow any visitor under the age of 13. If any parent feels that we have the information of children under the age of 13 years, they are requested to immediately contact us through **[Privacy](http://scoophub.in/privacy-policy-for-scoophub/)** and we will take immediate action to remove such information.

 **Privacy Policy is Strictly Observes over the Internet**

This policy document is strictly limited to your online access of our website. Any information that is collected offline is not compliant with this policy.

 **Consent**

Your use of our website is a proof that you agree to our privacy statements.

 **Update**

This privacy statement had been updated last on Tuesday, July 19th, 2016.

 _Whenever we make changes or amendments to our policy, they shall be updated here._
